<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<!--
      Adding objects into this xml file allows you to fetch more information about said
      object by right clicking the objects name in the Object selection box
      
      * IMPORTANT the @name attribute should always be lowercase, no matter the casing of the object in zip *
      
      If this file gets deleted or removed, an original copy will be made by the program.
-->
<ObjectInfo>
  <vehicles>
    <air>
      <object name="ahe_ah1z">
        <desc>The AH-1Z is the United States Marine Corps. attack helicopter.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/AH-1Z_Viper</link>
      </object>
      <object name="ahe_havoc">
        <desc>The Mi-28 is the MEC's attack helicopter.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/Mi-28_Havoc</link>
      </object>
      <object name="ahe_z10">
        <desc>The WZ-10 is the attack helicopter for the PLA.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/WZ-10</link>
      </object>
      <object name="air_f35b">
        <desc>
          The F-35B is the only VSTOL (Vertical/Short Take-Off and Landing) fighter jet in the game and one of the 
          four Fixed-Wing aircraft (F-35B, F-18, F-15E, A-10) used by the United States Marine Corps.
          It has no PLA or MEC counterpart and is only found on the USS Essex (LHD-2).
        </desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/F-35B</link>
      </object>
      <object name="air_j10">
        <desc>The J-10 in Battlefield 2 is the main fighter aircraft of the PLA</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/J-10</link>
      </object>
      <object name="air_su30mkk">
        <desc>The Su-30 in Battlefield 2 fullfills the role of a strike fighter for the PLA and as one of the three fixed-wing aircraft operated by the PLA</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/Su-30_Flanker-C</link>
      </object>
      <object name="chthe_z8">
        <desc>the Z-8 is used as the PLA transport helicopter. </desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/Z-8</link>
      </object>
      <object name="ruair_mig29">
        <desc>The MiG-29 is a jet operated by the Middle Eastern Coalition.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/MiG-29_Fulcrum</link>
      </object>
      <object name="ruair_su34">
        <desc>The Su-34 jet is the ground attack fighter for the MEC.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/Su-34_Fullback</link>
      </object>
      <object name="the_mi17">
        <desc>The Mi-17 is the MEC's main transport helicopter.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/Mi-17_Hip</link>
      </object>
      <object name="usair_f15">
        <desc>The F-15E in Battlefield 2 is one of the four fixed-wing aircraft used by the United States Marine Corps</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/F-15E_Strike_Eagle</link>
      </object>
      <object name="usair_f18">
        <desc>The F/A-18A Hornet appears in Battlefield 2 as one of the four USMC Fixed-wing aircraft in the game</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/F/A-18</link>
      </object>
      <object name="usthe_uh60">
        <desc>The MH-60S Knight Hawk is featured in Battlefield 2 as the USMC's transport helicopter</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/UH-60_Black_Hawk</link>
      </object>
    </air>
    <land>
      <object name="aav_tunguska">
        <desc>The 2K22 Tunguska is the MEC's anti-aircraft vehicle. It is also the equivalent of the USMC/EU M6 Linebacker and the PLA PGZ-95</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/2K22_Tunguska</link>
      </object>
      <object name="aav_type95">
        <desc>
          The PGZ-95 (referred as the type95 in the game files) is the PLA's anti-aircraft vehicle. It is also the equivalent of the USMC M6 Linebacker 
          and the MEC 2K22 Tunguska.
        </desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/Type_95_SPAAA</link>
      </object>
      <object name="apc_btr90">
        <desc>
          The BTR-90 appears in Battlefield 2 as the main Armored Personal Carrier (APC) used by the Middle Eastern Coalition, the Spetsnaz, Rebels, and Insurgents.
          Its counterparts are the Chinese WZ551 and the American LAV-25.
        </desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/BTR-90</link>
      </object>
      <object name="apc_wz551">
        <desc>the WZ551 is the Armored Personal Carrier (APC) used by the People's Liberation Army. Its counterparts are the USMC LAV-25 and the MEC BTR-90.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/WZ551</link>
      </object>
      <object name="jeep_faav">
        <desc>
          The Desert Patrol Vehicle is one of the 2 light vehicles operated by the United States Marine Corps and the European Union, operating alongside
          the HMMWV. It's counterpart is the FAV, which is operated by both the PLA and the MEC. Seats three players: a driver, a gunner, and a passenger.
        </desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/Desert_Patrol_Vehicle</link>
      </object>
      <object name="jep_mec_paratrooper">
        <desc>
          The FAV Buggy is used by the Middle Eastern Coalition, the MEC Special Forces, the People's Liberation Army, the Rebel Forces, the Insurgent Forces
          and the Spetsnaz. It performs similarly to the USMC Desert Patrol Vehicle and seats three players: a driver, a gunner, and a passenger.
        </desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/FAV</link>
      </object>
      <object name="jep_nanjing">
        <desc>The NJ 2046 is the light vehicle of the People's Liberation Army and can hold four players.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/NJ_2046</link>
      </object>
      <object name="jep_paratrooper">
        <desc>
          The FAV Buggy is used by the Middle Eastern Coalition, the MEC Special Forces, the People's Liberation Army, the Rebel Forces, the Insurgent Forces
          and the Spetsnaz. It performs similarly to the USMC Desert Patrol Vehicle and seats three players: a driver, a gunner, and a passenger.
        </desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/FAV</link>
      </object>
      <object name="jep_vodnik">
        <desc>The Vodnik is the medium transport vehicle of the Middle Eastern Coalition, Spetsnaz and the Russian Rebel Forces.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/GAZ-3937_Vodnik</link>
      </object>
      <object name="rutnk_t90">
        <desc>
          The T-90 is a main battle tank of the Middle Eastern Coalition. It is the counterpart to the USMC M1A2 Abrams, the PLA Type 98,
          and the EU Leopard 2 and Challenger 2.
        </desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/T-90</link>
      </object>
      <object name="tnk_type98">
        <desc>
          The Type 98 is the People's Liberation Army's main battle tank in Battlefield 2. Its counterparts are the American M1A2 Abrams, European Challenger 2
          and Leopard 2, and the MEC T-90.
        </desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/Type_98</link>
      </object>
      <object name="usaav_m6">
        <desc>The M6 Linebacker in Battlefield 2 is the main air-defense vehicle of the United States Marine Corps and the EU.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/M6_Linebacker</link>
      </object>
      <object name="usapc_lav25">
        <desc>The LAV-25 is an Armored Personal Carrier (APC) featured in Battlefield 2, operated by the United States Marine Corps.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/LAV-25</link>
      </object>
      <object name="usjep_hmmwv">
        <desc>
          The HMMWV is the light armored vehicle featured in Battlefield 2 for of United States Marine Corps and European Union and can hold up to
          4 players (1 driver, 1 gunner, 2 passengers).
        </desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/HMMWV</link>
      </object>
      <object name="ustnk_m1a2">
        <desc>
          The M1A2 is the main battle tank of the United States Marine Corps in Battlefield 2. It is the counterpart to the PLA Type 98,
          the EU Leopard 2 and Challenger 2, as well as the MEC T-90.
        </desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/M1A2_Abrams</link>
      </object>
    </land>
  </vehicles>
  <weapons>
    <handheld>
      <object name="chat_eryx">
        <desc>The ERYX is issued as the default anti-tank weapon for the MEC PLA, MECSF, and Spetsnaz Anti-Tank kits.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/ERYX</link>
      </object>
      <object name="chlmg_type95">
        <desc>The Type 95 is the light machine gun issued to the PLA Support Kit.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/QBB-95</link>
      </object>
      <object name="chpis_qsz92">
        <desc>The QSZ-92 is a pistol weapon, issued to all of the PLA Kits</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/QSZ-92</link>
      </object>
      <object name="chpis_qsz92_silencer">
        <desc>The QSZ-92 Silenced, used by the PLA sniper Kit</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/QSZ-92</link>
      </object>
      <object name="chrif_type85">
        <desc>The Type 85 is the default PLA Anti-Tank kit submachine gun.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/Type_85</link>
      </object>
      <object name="chrif_type95">
        <desc>The QBZ-97 is the standard primary weapon of the PLA Special Forces kit</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/QBZ-95B</link>
      </object>
      <object name="chsht_norinco982">
        <desc>The NOR982 is a 12-gauge, pump-action combat shotgun, issued to the PLA Engineer kit.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/NOR982</link>
      </object>
      <object name="chsht_protecta">
        <desc>The DAO-12 is the Tier One unlock for the Anti-Tank Kit</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/DAO-12</link>
      </object>
      <object name="chsni_type88">
        <desc>The Type 88 is a standard Sniper Rifle for the PLA.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/QBU-88</link>
      </object>
      <object name="nshgr_flashbang">
        <desc>The Flashbang is a gadget featured in the Battlefield 2: Special Forces expansion for the Assault kit.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/Flashbang</link>
      </object>
      <object name="rulmg_pkm">
        <desc>The PKM is a Tier One unlock in Battlefield 2 for the Support kit.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/PKM</link>
      </object>
      <object name="rulmg_rpk74">
        <desc>The RPK-74 is a weapon for the MEC's Support Kit.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/RPK</link>
      </object>
      <object name="rupis_baghira">
        <desc>The MR-444 is a weapon issued as the standard sidearm of the Middle Eastern Coalition, Spetsnaz, MECSF, Rebels, and Insurgents</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/MR-444</link>
      </object>
      <object name="rupis_baghira_silencer">
        <desc>The MR-444 Silenced is a weapon issued to the Sniper kit for the Middle Eastern Coalition, Spetsnaz, MECSF, Rebels, and Insurgents</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/MR-444</link>
      </object>
      <object name="rurgl_gp25">
        <desc>The GP-25 is a weapon that is attached to the AK-47, issued uniquely to the PLA Assault kit.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/GP-25</link>
      </object>
      <object name="rurgl_gp30">
        <desc>The GP-30 is a weapon that is attached to the AK-101 assault rifle used by the MEC.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/GP-30</link>
      </object>
      <object name="rurif_ak101">
        <desc>The AK-101 is a weapon issued to the MEC as their service rifle for both the Assault and Medic kits</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/AK-101</link>
      </object>
      <object name="rurif_ak47">
        <desc>The AK-47 is the standard primary weapon for the PLA's Assault and Medic kits.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/AK-47</link>
      </object>
      <object name="rurif_bizon">
        <desc>the PP-19 "Bizon" is issued to the MEC Anti-Tank Kit.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/PP-19</link>
      </object>
      <object name="rurif_dragunov">
        <desc>The SVD is a weapon featured in Battlefield 2 for the MEC Sniper kit.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/SVD</link>
      </object>
      <!--
      <object name="rurif_gp25">
        <desc></desc>
        <link></link>
      </object>
      -->
      <!--
      <object name="rurif_gp3.">
        <desc></desc>
        <link></link>
      </object>
      -->
      <object name="rurrif_ak74u">
        <desc>The AK-74U is the standard primary weapon for the Special Forces on the MEC team</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/AKS-74u</link>
      </object>
      <object name="rusht_saiga12">
        <desc>The S12K is the default weapon for the Engineer kit for the MEC team</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/Saiga</link>
      </object>
      <object name="usatp_predator">
        <desc>The SRAW (also known as the Predator SRAW) is issued to the USMC, SEALs, SAS, and EU Anti-Tank kit.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/SRAW</link>
      </object>
      <object name="ushgr_m67">
        <desc>Hand grenades are standard issue to each playable faction.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/Grenade</link>
      </object>
      <object name="uslmg_m249saw">
        <desc>The M249 SAW is the first weapon unlocked in the Support kit for the United States Marine Corps</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/M249</link>
      </object>
      <object name="uspis_92fs">
        <desc>The 92FS is the USMC's and European Union's standard sidearm</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/M9</link>
      </object>
      <object name="uspis_92fs_silencer">
        <desc>The 92FS Silenced is issued to the USMC sniper kit</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/M9</link>
      </object>
      <object name="usrgl_m203">
        <desc>The M203 is a weapon Grenade Launcher attachment for the M16A2.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/M203</link>
      </object>
      <object name="usrif_g36c">
        <desc>The G36C is the Tier One unlock for the Special Forces kit</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/G36C</link>
      </object>
      <object name="usrif_G3a3">
        <desc>The G3 is the Tier 1 unlock for the Assault Kit</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/G3</link>
      </object>
      <object name="usrif_m16a2">
        <desc>The M16A2 is the standard assault rifle used by the USMC Assualt and Medic kits</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/M16</link>
      </object>
      <!--
      <object name="USRIF_M203">
        <desc></desc>
        <link></link>
      </object>
      -->
      <object name="usrif_m24">
        <desc>The M24 is the default sniper rifle for the USMC</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/M24</link>
      </object>
      <object name="usrif_m4">
        <desc>The M4 is the standard primary weapon for the USMC's Special Forces kit.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/M4_Carbine</link>
      </object>
      <object name="usrif_mp5_a3">
        <desc>The MP5 is the default submachine gun of the USMC Anti-tank kit</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/MP5</link>
      </object>
      <object name="usrif_remington11-87">
        <desc>The M11-87 is a weapon issued to the USMC Engineer Kit</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/M11-87</link>
      </object>
      <object name="usrif_sa80">
        <desc>The L85A1 unlock weapon</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/L85</link>
      </object>
      <object name="ussht_jackhammer">
        <desc>The MK3A1 is the Tier one unlock for the Engineer Kit.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/MK3A1</link>
      </object>
      <object name="ussni_m95_barret">
        <desc>The M95 is a Tier One unlock for the Sniper kit.</desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/M95</link>
      </object>
    </handheld>
    <stationary>
      <object name="ats_tow">
        <desc>
          The BGM-71 TOW is the stationary anti-tank launcher used by the USMC, US Navy SEALs, as well as the EU in Euro Force. 
          Its counterpart is the Chinese HJ-8.
        </desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/BGM-71_TOW</link>
      </object>
      <object name="ats_hj8">
        <desc>
          The HJ-8 is the stationary anti-tank launcher used by the People's Liberation Army and the Middle Eastern Coalition.
          Its counterpart is the USMC TOW.
        </desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/HJ-8</link>
      </object>
      <object name="igla_djigit">
        <desc>
          The Igla stationary anti-aircraft site used by the People's Liberation Army and Middle Eastern Coalition,
          with two missiles that lock on and track enemy aircraft.
        </desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/SA-18_Igla</link>
      </object>
      <object name="usaas_stinger">
        <desc>
          The Stinger stationary anti-aircraft site used by the USMC and European Union, with two missiles that lock on 
          and track enemy aircraft.
        </desc>
        <link>http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/FIM-92_Stinger</link>
      </object>
    </stationary>
  </weapons>
</ObjectInfo>
